{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the Pixar film, &quot;Toy Story&quot; what was the name of the child who owned the toys?",
      "correct_answer": "Andy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Edward",
        "Danny",
        "Matt"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What was the name of the sea witch in the 1989 Disney film &quot;The Little Mermaid&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Ursula",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Madam Mim",
        "Maleficent",
        "Lady Tremaine"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Who voices for Ruby in the animated series RWBY?",
      "correct_answer": "Lindsay Jones",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tara Strong",
        "Jessica Nigri",
        "Hayden Panettiere"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of the following did not feature in the cartoon &#039;Wacky Races&#039;?",
      "correct_answer": "The Dragon Wagon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Bouldermobile",
        "The Crimson Haybailer",
        "The Compact Pussycat"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which cartoon family lives in 742 Evergreen Terrace, Springfield USA?",
      "correct_answer": "The Simpsons",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Hills",
        "The Flintstones",
        "The Griffins"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of these is NOT a catchphrase used by Rick Sanchez in the TV show &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Slam dunk, nothing but net!",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hit the sack, Jack!",
        "Rikki-Tikki-Tavi, biatch!",
        "Wubba-lubba-dub-dub!"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Wendy O. Koopa appeared in the Super Mario DIC Cartoons, but what was she known as?",
      "correct_answer": "Kootie Pie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sweetie Pie",
        "Wendy Pie",
        "Honey Pie"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In My Little Pony, what is the name of Applejack&#039;s younger sister?",
      "correct_answer": "Apple Bloom",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Red Delicious",
        "Apple Sweets",
        "Apple Fritter"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In The Simpsons, which war did Seymour Skinner serve in the USA Army as a Green Beret?",
      "correct_answer": "Vietnam War",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "World War 2",
        "World War 1",
        "Cold War"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What is Everest&#039;s favorite food in the Nickelodeon/Nick Jr. series &quot;PAW Patrol&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Liver",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chicken",
        "Steak",
        "Caribou"
      ]
    }
  ]
}